hey yo let me put some gas in this
[ __ ] Year [ __ ] I a really talk
my [ __ ] in a minute like who the [ __ ]
these [ __ ] really think they talking
to like [ __ ] who [ __ ]
dumb in a [ __ ] a block Money Getting
spun like like what like a CL bag baby
this a what you want if for I want to
hear his yes [ __ ] that she want to be
my up God bless bless look I Ain even
got dress that I took come after y on
man baby here we go again real fat got a
double CH first that [ __ ] hate me then
this [ __ ] hates me and somehow they
link up and they become friends like how
[ __ ] pipe down Mo oh y imitating my sty
B [ __ ] red lips let me show you white
toes eating Yellow Tail like of no keep
a hater obsess in my comments having a
dick sucking contest I'm pressure y
press yall don't get a dress getting out
dressed look it's a look when I'm
hopping out the beat red WI hanging down
to my knees it's your birthday but they
talking about me why you mad take a
picture say cheat you dumb you slow you
wi got your first P now you sty
everything you got a high five years
before I put it on the ground for even
hit the store up classy and a [ __ ] block
Money Getting SP like like what like a
CL bag baby this what you want if I ask
for I want to hear is yes [ __ ] say she
want to be my God blessed look I Ain
even got dress any out that I took come
after watch ass on man I know y [ __ ]
be hting looking this good is really
exhausting that his don't coasting just
got my laser [ __ ] move like a do top
not [ __ ] get the most not the less sir
[ __ ] look big like their triester
every time I post these [ __ ] get
stress sir y be putting on [ __ ] I never
[ __ ] be haing on the low I PE it if I
say anything mean I mean it I ain't
never lost no [ __ ] I need it I'm rich
I ain't getting no pool that's not H it
big ass Y and I'm having sex on it her
life so trash think I put a head on it
[ __ ] be laughing like what's funny
bragging on a niggaer that be dying [ __ ]
mey in a [ __ ] BL Money Getting SP like
like what like a clb baby this a what
you want if I ask for I want to hear is
yes [ __ ] say she want to be my got
blessed look I Ain got dress any out
that I took come after y on
[Music]
man yeah
yeah
okay okay